question_data = [
    {
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "category": "Entertainment: Television",
        "question": "In &quot;Star Trek: The Next Generation&quot;, Data is the only android in existence.",
        "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "History",
     "question": "Kublai Khan is the grandchild of Genghis Khan?", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
     "question": "Shang Tsung is a playable character in Mortal Kombat XL.", "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Music",
     "question": "A Saxophone is a brass instrument.", "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Science &amp; Nature",
     "question": "Not including false teeth; A human has two sets of teeth in their lifetime.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
     "question": "In Resident Evil 4, the Chicago Typewriter has infinite ammo.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Animals", "question": "Rabbits can&#039;t vomit.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "General Knowledge",
     "question": "The bikini is named after the &quot;Bikini Atoll&quot;, an island where the United States conducted tests on atomic bombs.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Board Games",
     "question": "In the Dungeons and Dragons universe, Beshaba is the deity of bad luck. ",
     "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime &amp; Manga",
     "question": "In Full Metal Panic!, Whispered are those who are capable of creating Black Technology.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}]
